Guide to the Campbell Family Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Correspondence, 1880s-1972; Series I
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1936 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 181)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 182)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 183)
  - Dorothy Campbell - incl. letter from Chi Ki-Kwong re: 1929 attack by pirates, 1940-1943 (Box 9, Folder 184)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 185)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1945 Feb-May (Box 10, Folder 186)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1945 Jul-Aug (Box 10, Folder 187)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1945 Sep-Nov 9 (Box 10, Folder 188)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1945 Nov 18-Dec, c.1945-1946 (Box 10, Folder 189)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1946 Jan-May (Box 10, Folder 190)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1946 Aug-Sep (Box 10, Folder 191)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1946 Oct-Nov (Box 10, Folder 192)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1946 Dec, n.m. (Box 10, Folder 193)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1947 Jan-Feb (Box 10, Folder 194)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1947 Mar-Dec (Box 10, Folder 195)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1948, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 196)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1950, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 197)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1952, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 198)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1954,1955, 1954-1958 (Box 10, Folder 199)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 200)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 201)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1963, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 202)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Material re: War Claims for losses in China, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 203)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1966-1969 (Box 10, Folder 204)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1970, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 205)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Letter from Marion Reith to her parents--describing Swatow, Kakchieh, and Kityang; letter from Dr. Marguerite Everham to "girls", 1936, c. 1938, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 206)
  - David Campbell, 1929, 1937, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 207)
  - David Campbell, c. 1951-1956 (Box 11, Folder 208)
  - David Campbell, 1957-1961 (Box 11, Folder 209)
  - David Campbell, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 210)
  - David Campbell, 1964-1966 (Box 11, Folder 211)
  - David Campbell, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 212)
  - David Campbell, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 213)
  - David Campbell, 1969 Jan-Apr (Box 11, Folder 214)
  - David Campbell, 1969 May-Aug (Box 11, Folder 215)
  - David Campbell, 1969 Sep-Dec (Box 11, Folder 216)
  - David Campbell, 1970 Jan-Jul (Box 11, Folder 217)
  - David Campbell fragment, 1970 Aug-1971 (Box 11, Folder 218)
  - David Campbell, Jr. to Dorothy Campbell, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 219)
  - Bessie G. Campbell (Mrs. David), 1935-c. 1956 (Box 11, Folder 220)
- Diaries and Notebooks, 1855-1968; Series II
  Material in this series is arranged chronologically. In the case of the Louise Campbell material, diaries appear first, followed by notebooks, then account books, etc. Diaries and Notebooks occasionally overlap in form, as well as in dates.
  - George Campbell: Diary, 1874 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - George Campbell: Diary, 1877-1878 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - George Campbell: Autograph Book, 1879-1894 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - George Campbell: A Manual of Church History - used at Baptist Theological Seminary, Morgan Park, Ill., with notes in Chinese, 1880 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - George Campbell: Diary excerpts (typed)-- incl. courtship letter to Jennie Wortman, 1882-1883 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - George Campbell: Diary, 1888 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - George Campbell: "Observations with Transit", 1896-1897 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - George Campbell: Diary (begins at back), 1896-1898 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - George Campbell: Diary (begins at back), 1902, 1910-1911 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - George Campbell: Account Book and Notes, 1912 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - George Campbell: Diary, 1912-1916 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - George Campbell: Notebook/Diary, 1913 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - George Campbell: Notebook, c. 1913-1914 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - George Campbell: Notebook, 1914 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - George Campbell: Notebook, 1914 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - George Campbell: Notebook, 1914 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - George Campbell: Diary, 1924-1925 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - George Campbell: Notebook, 1914 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - George Campbell: Notebook, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - George Campbell: Notebook re: Genealogy, c. 1925 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Notes (loose-leaf) for classes, talks, etc., 1924-1927 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Thomas P. Campbell: Diary, 1855-1857 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Jennie W. Campbell: Autograph Book, 1879 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Jennie W. Campbell: Autograph Book, 1881 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Jennie W. Campbell: Diary, 1881-1882 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Jennie W. Campbell: Birthday Book with Notes, 1887-c. 1920 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Jennie W. Campbell: Book of Quotations, c. 1910 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Jennie W. Campbell: Guest Book, 1917-1935 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Jennie W. Campbell: Diary, with a few entries made by George Campbell, 1927-1930 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Jennie W. Campbell: Diary, 1928-1934 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Jennie W. Campbell: Diary, 1935-1939 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Louise Campbell: Diary, 1895 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Louise Campbell: Diary, 1902 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Louise Campbell: Diary, 1909 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Louise Campbell: Diary, 1913 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Louise Campbell: Diary, 1914 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Louise Campbell: Diary, 1915 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Louise Campbell: Diary, 1916 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Louise Campbell: Diary, 1917-1921 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Louise Campbell: Diary, with two pressed leaves enclosed, 1922-1926 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Louise Campbell: Diary, 1927-1931 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Louise Campbell: Diary, typed excerpts re: family reunion of 1935, 1932-1936 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Louise Campbell: Diary, 1937-1941 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Louise Campbell: Diary, typed excerpts, 1942-1946 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Louise Campbell: Diary, 1947-1951 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Louise Campbell: Diary, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Louise Campbell: Diary, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Louise Campbell: Diary, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Louise Campbell: Diary, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Louise Campbell: Diary, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Louise Campbell: Diary, 1957-1961 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Louise Campbell: Diary, 1962-1965 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Louise Campbell: Diary, 1966-1968 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Louise Campbell: Record of her first year as a missionary, 1911 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Louise Campbell: Notebook, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Louise Campbell: Notebook (small), 1943 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Louise Campbell: Notebook, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Louise Campbell: Notebook, 1957-1961 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Louise Campbell: Notebook, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Louise Campbell: Notebook, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Louise Campbell: Notebook, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Louise Campbell: Notebooks (2), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Louise Campbell: Notebook--written in Chinese, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Louise Campbell: Birthday Book, 1890 (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Louise Campbell: Account Book, 1947-1950 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Louise Campbell: Sunday School Class Roll Book, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Louise Campbell: Datebooks (4), 1954, 1965, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Louise Campbell: Correspondence Record, incl. Medical Report, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Louise Campbell: Misc. Small Notebooks (5), 1958,1966,1967, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - Louise Campbell: "Chinese Medical Remedies- Notes by Anna Foster"--cures practiced by the Hakkas, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - Margaret Campbell Burket: Birthday Book, 1890-c. 1912 (Box 22, Folder 71)
  - Margaret Campbell Burket: Diary--typed copy (20 pp.), 1904-1907 (Box 22, Folder 72)
  - Dorothy Campbell: 1 p. list of diaries and notebooks (incomplete) (Box 23, Folder 73)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary, 1908, 1912 (Box 23, Folder 74)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary, 1914-1919 (Box 23, Folder 75)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary/Notebook, 1920-1921 (Box 23, Folder 76)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary/Notebook, 1921, 1928 (Box 23, Folder 77)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary, 1926 (Box 23, Folder 78)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary, 1926-1931 (Box 23, Folder 79)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary, 1929,1932-1933,1936 (Box 23, Folder 80)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Notebook, 1930-1931 (Box 23, Folder 81)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary, 1932 (Box 23, Folder 82)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary, 1934 (Box 24, Folder 83)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary, 1935-1941 (Box 24, Folder 84)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Notebook, 1928, 1936-1938 (Box 24, Folder 85)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary, 1938-1944 (Box 24, Folder 86)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Notebook, 1939, 1943-1944 (Box 24, Folder 87)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary/Notebook, 1939, 1941-1943 (Box 24, Folder 88)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Notebook, ca. 1940 (Box 24, Folder 89)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary, 1942,1944-1946, ca.1950 (Box 24, Folder 90)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary/Notebook, 1943-1944 (Box 24, Folder 91)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary, 1943-1944 (Box 24, Folder 92)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary/Notebook, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 93)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Notebook, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 94)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Notebook, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 95)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Notebook, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 96)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Notebook, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 97)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary, 1944 Dec 1945 Jan (Box 25, Folder 98)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary, 1945 Mar 1946 Sep (Box 25, Folder 99)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Notebook, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 100)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Notebook, 1942, 1945-1946 (Box 25, Folder 101)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Notebook, 1945-1946, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 102)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Notebook, 1945-1946 (Box 25, Folder 103)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Notebook (enclosure), 1944-1945, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 104)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary, 1947-1949 (Box 25, Folder 105)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary, 1949-1952 (Box 26, Folder 106)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary/Notebook, 1948-1952 (Box 26, Folder 107)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary/Notebook, 1951-1953 (Box 26, Folder 108)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary/Notebook, 1951-1953 (Box 26, Folder 109)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary/Notebook, 1953-1954 (Box 26, Folder 110)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary, 1953-1954 (Box 26, Folder 111)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary, 1954-1957 (Box 26, Folder 112)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 113)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary, 1957-1960 (Box 26, Folder 114)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary, 1960-1965 (Box 26, Folder 115)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Diary/Notebook, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 116)
- Writings, 1880-1972; Series III
  Material is filed chronologically according to generation, and according to classification. (e.g.--essays, term papers, etc.)
  - George Campbell: "Talk" delivered to Spokane, WA. Baptists; "The Whale or the Goat"--2 pp. article, 1913, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Jennie Campbell: Material re: Baptist missionary work among the Hakkas of China, 1932 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Jennie Campbell: "A man's best things lie nearest him" (2 pp.) with pressed flowers, fragment, 1880, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Jennie Campbell: Autobiographical Material, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Louise Campbell: Term papers re: China and India, 1926-1927 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Miriam Campbell Joyce: "In Appreciation"--essay, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Thomas P. Campbell: "Story of his Travels. As found written in one of the note books of his father." (1 p.--typed) (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Autobiographical Sketches, 1946, c. 1960 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Dorothy Campbell: "Japanese Prisoner--A Play" (2 copies); letters from Woman's American Baptist Foreign Mission Society and Columbia University, 1945, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Dorothy Campbell: "The Mess in Nursing"--article; electrostatic copies of letters re: article from Pearl S. Buck and "Woman's Home Companion", 1955, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Dorothy Campbell: "Mental Health and Psychiatric Nursing"--4 graduate school papers, 1963, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Dorothy Campbell: "Psychology of Family Relations"--3 graduate school papers, 1963, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Material re: horoscope, c. 1970 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Material re: lecture series by Dr. Ira Progoff, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Autobiographical Material, 1945, 1969, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Autobiographical Material, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Autobiographical Material re: Terms 1-3 in China, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Biographical Sketch written by Marie Naismith, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Essays, case study, etc., ca. 1930-1946 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Essays, travelogue, etc., 1948-1951 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Essays, travelogue, etc., 1956-ca. 1968 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Manuscript of a three-act play, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Essays, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Misc., n.d. (Box 27, Folder 24-26)
  - David Campbell: "Account of His Adventures", 1927 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - David Campbell: "The Chinese Sport of Bull Fighting " -essay, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - David Campbell: Essays, term paper, article, 1957-1972 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - David Campbell: "Flash Flood", "Dawn or Twilight" --essays, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 30)
- Personal Items and Memorabilia, 1868-1972; Series IV
  Material is arranged chronologically according to generation. Biographical data appears first, followed by the material of individual members of the Campbell family. A photograph section is located at the end of the series. A separate box contains oversized printed material, primarily magazine and newspaper clippings. NB: The Campbell Family Papers complement the papers of the Foster Family, Record Group No. 1. Two generations of the families were friends and co-workers in South China.
  - Biographical Material: Genealogy of the descendants of George and Jennie Campbell--prepared by David Campbell (2 copies) (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Biographical Material: "Family Record"--births and deaths (1 p.) (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Biographical Material re: George and Jennie Campbell (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Biographical Material re: George Campbell (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Biographical Material re: Jennie W. Campbell--"Comments About Mother by Her Three Youngest Children" (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Biographical Material re: Louise Campbell (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Biographical Material re: Louise Campbell--transcript of a tape about Kaying Girls School and other China tales (14 pp.--1967) (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Biographical Material re: Miriam C. Joyce, Paul W. Campbell, Thomas P. Campbell, and Kenneth M. Campbell (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Biographical Material re: Margaret C. Burket and Everett S. Burket (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Biographical Material re: Dorothy M. Campbell pp. 1-16 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Biographical Material re: Dorothy M. Campbell pp. 17-30 (Autobio. Sketches) (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Biographical Material re: David M. Campbell (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Thomas P. Campbell: "History of the Delavan Baptist Church, Delavan, Illinois, From 1846 to 1906" (87 pp.)--p. 44-47 re: TPC (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Mary Campbell: Memorials with a covering letter from Mrs. H. A. McKeene of the Illinois Farmers' Institute (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Mary Campbell: Newspaper and Magazine Clippings--incl. letter re: M.C. written by her brother, George Campbell; Silhouette, Postcard (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - George Campbell: Genealogical Material--"Record of Family Traits" forms from the Eugenics Record Office (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - George Campbell: Genealogical Material (Box 29, Folder 17-20)
  - George Campbell: Genealogical Material (printed) (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - George Campbell: Material re: Milk Goat Industry (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - George Campbell: Account of 1915 illness, with letter from Dr. H. W. Newman to "Miss Campbell" (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - George Campbell: Material re: his death (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Jennie Campbell: Material re: her death, incl. a letter from the Toledo Council of Churches (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - George Campbell: Misc. printed material--"The American Orientalist", V. II, No. 12 (1905), 1 Chinese language pamphlet (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - George Campbell: Pamphlets (2)--"Proceedings of the Second and Fourth Annual Session of the Palouse Baptist. ... Spokane, W. T." (l883, 1885) (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - George Campbell: Pamphlets (3)- "Origin and Migration of the Hakkas" by George Campbell (1912) (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Louise Campbell: Birth certificate (negative copy), fingerprints, medical material (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Louise Campbell: Floor Plans, Lists, etc. (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Louise Campbell: Maps of China (2) (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Louise Campbell: Newspaper and Magazine Clippings from Baptist and Chinese publications (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Louise Campbell: Newspaper and Magazine Clippings re: LC (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Louise Campbell: Pamphlets (4)--"Missionary Cameralogs", "Who's Who in the So. China Mission", "Then and Now", "Second Annual Report of the Hakka Work...1906" (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Louise Campbell: Postcards, etc. of trip to South America (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Louise Campbell: Professional Material (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Miriam Campbell Joyce: Material re: family and residence (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Thomas P. Campbell: Memorial card, newspaper article (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Margaret C. and Everett Burket: Memorial services of both, resume of MCB, etc. (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Margaret C. Burket: "Breeze in the Bamboos"--printed poems by Dorothy Louise Burket (33 pp. ) (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Kenneth Campbell: Chronology of his house, movings, etc. (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Brochures (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Extracts from Jung and Erich Fromm (typed) (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Invitation, Book Jacket, Lists, etc. (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Material re: Bible Institute of Los Angeles, Clifton Springs Sanitarium and Clinic (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Material re: nursing--diploma, graduation program and photo (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Newspaper and Magazine Clippings (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Newspaper and Magazine Clippings (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Obituaries of former missionaries, material re: D.C. (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - Dorothy Campbell: Scrapbook--New York vacation (1947) (Box 30, Folder 50)
  - David Campbell: Floor plan, etc. (Box 30, Folder 51)
  - Photographs: Assortment of "Old Family Photos", incl. 2 tintypes (Box 30, Folder 52)
  - Photographs: Campbell Ancestors--incl. Thomas P. Campbell (Box 30, Folder 53)
  - Photographs: George Campbell and Jennie Wortman prior to their marriage, school and family scenes (Box 30, Folder 54)
  - Photographs: Family Portrait (1902) (Box 30, Folder 55)
  - Photographs: Mary Campbell (1 photo, 1 tintype); State School for Girls, Grand Mound, WA.- girls gardening, sewing, etc. (14) (Box 30, Folder 56)
  - Photographs and Identification Lists: China Inland Mission School, Chefoo, No. China--group photos incl. Thornton Wilder (from Kenneth Campbell) (Box 30, Folder 57)
  - Scrapbook: Postcards of China (Box 30, Folder 58)
  - Feb. "Our Missionary Helper" - letter from George Campbell, p. 1; Letter from Jennie Campbell, p. 2., 1908 (Box OVd7)
  - "Desert Weed Provides Wax" - newspaper article, 1925
  - Louise Campbell's Bachelor of Arts degree from Occidental College, 1927
  - Dec. 9 Hong Kong Telegraph - article re: Haiching Incident, 1929
  - Dec. 10 Los Angeles Times - article re: Haiching Incident, 1929
  - Seattle newspaper - article re: Haiching Incident, 1929
  - "Young People" - article by Louise Campbell, 1932
  - Newspaper article re. Dorothy Campbell and Miriam Campbell Joyce